美国谍梦
尽在人人影视
还记得我吗  队长
Remember me, captain?
《边桥谜案》前情提要
Previously on The Bridge..
另一头是什么
What's on the other end?
一个疯婊子
A crazy, psychotic bitch.
你想让我对付她
You want me to deal with her.
如果一切属实
If everything checks out,
一切就和卡尔在世时一样  只是换成雷
it'll be just like it was with Karl, but with Ray.
我在这边想做点生意
I want to get something going down here.
明白我的意思吗
You know what I mean?
-当然  -好极了
- I do. - Sweet.
车里有拦网
像是警车那种
对
-你呼叫支援了吗  -没有
- Did you call in unit?  - No.
是真警车吗
Is that a real police cruiser?
不是  他肯定是在拍卖会上买的
No. Guy must've bought an '02 Crow Vic
02款福特皇冠维多利亚
at auction and tricked it up
伪装成警车的样子
to look like one.
-技术人员正在取证  -吉娜听到他父亲
- The lab's all over it. - Gina heard her father
遇害前在和人谈话
talking to someone before th murder
你认为凶手是他的病人  是吗
You're thinking that the killer was a patient, right?
有可能
Maybe.
他的面颊长什么样  丰满的还是深陷的
What about his cheeks? Full? Hollow?
当时很黑  我躲在那里只看了他一眼
It was dark. I was hiding, and I only saw him for a second.
女性  白种人
Female, Caucasian
十五岁  穿黑白毛衣...
15 years old, black and whit sweater...
吉娜
Gina.
撑住...
Hey! Okay..
他一直在监视我们
He' watching us.
你还好吗
Are you all right?
我很喜欢你这副
I'm digging the whole
艾莉卡・芭朵的打扮[美国歌手]
Erykah Badu thing you got going.
你的头巾
The turban.
你想怎么样
What do you want?
这是我们的首次合作
Ah, I thought it would be nice doing this in person you know,
还是面谈比较好
seeing it's the first time and all.
还想怎么样
What else do yo want?
看来
I'm guessing I, uh...
那个牛仔律师核实过我的信息了
checked out with the cowboy lawyer?
蒙特做事很仔细
Monte's very thorough.
好吧  那就是没问题了
Okay. So I check out.
请现在把钱给我吧
I'd like my money now, please.
-有问题吗  -没问题
- Something wrong? - I'm good.
-那就滚吧  -我在想
- Then we're done. - Yeah, well, you know...
我们可以来个双向贸易
I was thinking about getting a little two-way commerce going.
那条隧道只做单向的真是太可惜了
It's a shame to see that tunnel running one way.
你有什么计划
What do you have in mind?
AR-15自动步枪  五十支起运
AR-15s. Say, 50 to start.
从这边运出去
We go from there.
现在要弄到这种枪可不容易
That's not an easy weapon to get right now.
那是
No shit.
你怎么看
So what do you say?
枪包在我身上
I got a great connect.
这周就能到货
I can deliver this week.
你觉得口交怎么样
Do you have an opinion about oral sex?
这个啊  挺好的
Uh, yeah. It's, uh... it's cool.
我很喜欢
I prefer it.
有些女士的确好这口
Some ladies do.
这就是我们的协议  快点
This will be our arrangement, moving forward.
那你是同意运枪了
So is that a yes on the guns?
要看你活儿了
Depende.
贩毒集团都这样吗
Is this a cartel thing?
闭嘴
那好吧
Okay, then.
m 325 0 l 355 0 l 332 47 l 354 47 l 399 136 l 369 136 l 328 53 l 288 136 l 257 136 l 325 0 m 467 0 l 497 0 l 474 47 l 496 47 l 541 136 l 511 136 l 470 53 l 430 136 l 399 136 l 467 0 m 545 1 l 583 1 l 583 14 l 568 14 l 568 19 l 583 19 l 583 30 l 568 30 l 568 34 l 599 34 l 599 30 l 583 30 l 583 19 l 599 19 l 599 14 l 583 14 l 583 1 l 611 1 b 616 1 622 6 622 10 l 622 36 l 652 0 l 678 0 l 644 41 l 622 41 l 622 47 l 596 47 l 597 54 l 625 54 l 625 68 l 541 68 l 541 54 l 572 54 l 571 47 l 545 47 l 545 1 m 583 72 l 583 85 l 569 85 l 569 90 l 598 90 l 598 85 l 583 85 l 583 72 l 611 72 b 615 72 621 78 621 82 l 653 44 l 678 44 l 644 86 l 621 86 l 621 103 l 597 103 l 597 136 l 570 136 l 564 126 l 562 136 l 542 136 l 548 107 l 568 107 l 565 121 l 571 121 l 571 103 l 547 103 l 547 72 l 583 72 m 600 107 l 620 107 l 624 124 l 653 89 l 679 89 l 642 136 l 615 136 l 618 132 l 606 132 l 600 107 m 689 0 l 716 0 l 721 15 l 732 15 l 732 30 l 718 56 l 731 56 l 735 100 l 721 100 l 717 59 l 714 64 l 714 136 l 693 136 l 693 79 l 676 79 l 707 30 l 679 30 l 679 15 l 694 15 l 689 0 m 738 0 l 804 0 b 807 0 813 6 813 9 l 813 87 l 794 87 l 794 14 l 756 14 l 756 87 l 763 77 l 763 21 l 787 21 l 787 91 l 798 91 l 798 120 l 820 120 l 812 136 l 778 136 l 778 90 l 748 136 l 723 136 l 756 87 l 738 87 l 738 0 m 257 151 l 275 151 l 297 182 l 319 151 l 337 151 l 304 197 l 304 227 l 290 227 l 290 197 l 257 151 m 337 151 l 355 151 l 377 182 l 399 151 l 417 151 l 384 197 l 384 227 l 370 227 l 370 197 l 337 151 m 425 192 l 447 192 b 445 181 427 181 425 192 l 410 192 b 414 162 458 162 462 192 l 462 206 l 425 206 b 425 210 429 212 433 213 l 462 213 l 462 227 l 433 227 b 412 227 408 203 410 192 m 462 151 l 532 151 l 532 165 l 504 165 l 504 227 l 489 227 l 489 165 l 462 165 l 462 151 m 580 172 l 580 186 l 549 186 b 543 186 543 192 549 192 l 565 192 b 589 192 589 227 565 227 l 532 227 l 532 213 l 565 213 b 570 213 570 206 565 206 l 549 206 b 524 206 524 172 549 172 l 580 172 m 592 213 l 606 213 l 606 227 l 592 227 l 592 213 m 639 172 l 665 172 l 665 186 l 639 186 b 623 186 623 213 639 213 l 665 213 l 665 227 l 639 227 b 603 227 603 172 639 172 m 700 184 b 722 184 722 215 700 215 l 700 229 b 740 229 740 170 700 170 b 660 170 660 229 700 229 l 700 215 b 680 215 680 184 700 184 m 737 172 l 782 172 b 803 172 813 177 813 198 l 813 228 l 799 228 l 799 198 b 799 186 793 187 782 187 l 782 228 l 768 228 l 768 187 l 752 187 l 752 228 l 737 228 l 737 172
m 20 0 l 209 0 b 218 0 229 11 229 20 l 229 209 b 229 218 218 228 209 228 l 20 228 b 11 228 0 218 0 209 l 0 20 b 0 11 11 0 20 0
m 115 64 l 115 35 l 171 0 l 177 0 l 133 46 l 143 52 l 179 0 l 184 0 l 159 63 l 229 107 l 229 182 l 145 96 l 135 122 l 207 227 l 137 227 l 115 172 l 115 93 l 126 76 l 115 64 l 104 76 l 115 93 l 115 172 l 93 227 l 23 227 l 95 122 l 84 96 l 0 182 l 0 107 l 70 63 l 45 0 l 50 0 l 87 52 l 97 46 l 52 0 l 59 0 l 115 35
m 71 60 b 71 0 161 0 161 60 b 161 120 71 120 71 60
仅供学习 禁止用于任何商业盈利行为
更多影视更新
请登陆www.YYeTs.com
翻译
圈圈
屯栗子
爱卿遛小鸟
翻译
蓬蓬裙
lulu
foolyangyang
校对
面条打包子
wdjmhs
时间轴
爱卿遛小鸟
imok
chance-coco
后期  吉吉
总监  wdjmhs
边桥谜案
第一季   第七集
命运
Destino
你在干什么
What are you doing?
查通话记录
Call log.
过去五年的被盗车辆报告
Stolen vehicle reports from the past five years.
你起床多久了
How long have you been up?
凶手在某处弄到了车
The killer got that car somewhere.
也许在这里  也许在达拉斯或者芝加哥
Yeah, maybe here, maybe in Dallas, maybe Chicago.
你能处理的信息是有限的
You know, there's only so much information you can process.
你有更好的主意吗
Well, do you have better idea?
你喜欢研究细节  跟凶手一样
You like details, huh? Just like the killer.
这是我的工作方式
It's how I work.
也许你有时该听从直觉
Maybe you should listen to your gut sometimes.
我回警局再看看那辆车
I'm going in to look at that car again.
别把杯子放在那上面
Don't leave that up there.
抱歉
Oh, yeah. Sorry.
我想回家跟阿尔玛谈谈
Think I'm gonna go home and talk to Alma.
她不会让你回家住的
She's not gonna let you back into the house.
你的直觉应该这么告诉你的
Your gut should tell you that.
也许我该去住酒店
Yeah, maybe I should find a hotel, huh?
我家沙发怎么了
What's wrong with the couch?
没什么  等一下
Nothing. Yep. Oh, hold on.
差点忘了  给你
I almost forgot. Here.
这是干什么
What's that for?
买花的钱
For the flowers.
给吉蒂买的花  我不是向你借过钱吗
For Kitty. See, I borrowed some money.
现在还给你
So I'm paying you back.
对  谢谢
Okay. Thank you.
客气  该我谢谢你
Yeah. Thank you.
牙套取下来之后
What's th first thing you're gonna eat
你最先要吃什么
when these things come off?
别说话  坚持住
Don't talk. Hold on.
我手头有件大案
I'm working the case of a lifetime.
好  行了
Yeah, all right.
是跟专案组合作的
I'm working with task force.
知道了
All right.
需要保密  所以不能跟你说
Confidential stuff, can't... tell you about it.
搞定了
All righty.
我发誓  我真的不在乎她
我不相信你
你是来拿衣服的吗
还是来骚扰我的
我们不要把问题变得更复杂
没有  你只是跟那个女人上床了而已
现在你又跟你的搭档上床
桑娅吗  当然没有
昨晚你在哪里睡的
在她的公寓里  但是
我没跟她上床  我睡的沙发
难以置信
我想回来住
我想跟我的家人  跟你在一起
但我不想让你回来
既然你这么说
格斯要退学了
如果你这么在意你的家人  就去跟他谈谈
我要去上班了
我不想回来还看到你在这里
-喂  -克罗斯警探
- Hello? - Detective Cross?
-对  是我  -我好像找到了
- Yes, I'm here. - I think I found it.
车的交易地点是
The car was purchased at...
关于车我找到了点线索
I got something on the car.
马可去哪了
Where's Marco at?
他回家跟妻子争辩去了
He went home to argue with his wife.
好吧  车有什么线索
Right. What about the car?
从发动机上找到了车辆识别码中的三位数
They pulled three digits of a VIN from the engine block.
但和所有挂失的皇冠维多利亚都不匹配
Doesn't match any stolen Crown Vics.
说下去
Go on.
但是与五年前在拉斯・克鲁塞斯的
But I have a partial match on a car
一个拍卖会上卖出的一辆车
that was sold by a auction
有部分匹配
in Las Cruces five years ago.
我跟拍卖行那边打了一上午电话
I've been on the phone with the auction house all morning.
他们把交易记录找出来了
They dug up the sale.
有买主的名字吗
Is there a name?
杰克森・柴德里斯  住在麦克纳特路
Jack Childress, lives out on McNutt Road.
十年前残疾了
He's been on disability for the last ten years.
值得去查查
Well, that's worth a look.
抱歉  我迟到了
Sorry, I'm late.
家里情况怎么样了
How's things at home?
很糟  可能还恶化了
Bad. Maybe worse.
很遗憾
Sorry to hear that.
世事如此
It is what it is.
你去跟着桑娅吧
Why don't you stick with Sonya.
她要去沙漠里追查一点线索
She's gonna follow up a dice lead out in the desert.
知道了
Copy that.
-宝贝  -你在干什么呢
- Hey, baby. - What are you doing?
勘察排水管
I'm investigating the drain.
当起我的游泳池清理工了吗
You're my pool boy now?
我想夏天找点活干  夫人
Well, I was looking for summer work, ma'am.
-你见过她了吗  -见过了  也拿到钱了
- Did you see her?  - Yeah. And I got the money.
她还说什么了吗
Did she say anything else?
没有
Nope.
就是这里
This is the place.
这家伙有犯罪记录吗
This guy has record?
马可
Marco.
不准靠近
埃尔帕索警局  打开门
El Paso PD. Open the door!
埃尔帕索警局  我们有搜查证
El Paso PD, search warrant.
有人在家吗
Anybody home?
有人在吗
Is anybody here?
这到底是什么
What the hell is this?
那是什么
What's that?
《北埃尔帕索城辩证法》
The Dialectics of El Paso del Norte.
杰克森・柴德里斯著
By Jackson Childress.
大发现啊
What the hell?
我们找对人了
This is our guy.
我们不一定非做不可
We don't have to do this.
可是
Well...
我们都想这样  对吗
it's what we both want, right?
但你是有夫之妇
But you're married.
我们可以再等等  等时机合适
We could wait... and do it right.
什么意思
What do you mean?
如果你想离婚  就先把婚离了
If you want to get a divorce, get a divorce.
没那么简单
Well, that' complicated.
对  是有点麻烦
Yeah. A little.
看样子这家伙疯得不轻啊
I think he's off his meds.
见鬼  条子来了
Oh, shit. Cops.
第九章
Chapter Nine:
论墨西哥民族的外星血统
On the Extraterrestrial Origins of the Mexican people's.
这混蛋脑子不正常
他是个疯子
He's insane.
你看  他去过墨西哥
Look. He's been to Mexico.
他说自己是去"执行任务"
Many times he calls them his "missions".
我觉得应该把专案组叫来
Well, I think we should bring in the task force.
不  只叫汉克  他已经在路上了
No. Just Hank. He's on his way.
我们上一次汇报的时候  是他在接听
Last time we broadcast something, he was listening.
我们先撤  等他到了再行动
We pull back and wait for him to come.
你同意白天见我  倒让我吃了一惊
I was surprised you were willing to meet me during the day.
世事无常
Well, everything' changing.
旧貌新颜
Shell of the egg is breaking.
-又有活让我干了  -是的
- You have another job for me?  - I do.
-叫什么名字  -她叫萨尔・维加
- What's her name?  - Her name is Sar Vega.
是我的女儿
She's my daughter.
她辍学了  迷失了自己
She dropped out of school. She lost her way.
你想让我把她带走吗
Do you want me to take her?
不顾她的个人意愿  强行带去鲍勃那吗
Take her to Bob's? Against her will?
我希望你能和她谈谈
I want you to talk to her.
-我的话她听不进去  -我不是传话的
- She won't listen to me anymore.  - I'm not a messenger.
我只负责送人
I'm a conduit.
我已经束手无策了
I don't know what else to do.
好了  别哭了
Okay, don't cry.
好吧  我干
All right, I'll do it.
你帅呆了  老爹
真的吗
您最近有一点点发福
你看起来帅呆了  陛下
你刚刚说了什么
对不起  先生  对不起
混账东西
说话小心点  混蛋
我喜欢看你穿西装
超性感
谢谢你  亲爱的
我想去那边看看鞋
就在街那头接我好了
过来
让奥夫雷贡跟你一起吧
不用了  没事  他还要保护你呢
冷静  没事
Easy. Easy, easy
求你了  别伤害我
没事  不要怕
Don't... don't be scared.
-是你妈妈让我来的  -搞什么鬼
- Your mother sent me. - What's the hell?
她希望你过得好  我也是
She wants a bette life for you. So do I.
我知道你是谁
I know who you are.
你是我妈妈手下的那个傻逼白鬼
You're my mother's stupid gringo coyote.
我不觉得自己是什么
Well, I don't consider myself...
我在我的成人礼上见过你  白痴
I met you at my quinceaera, idiot.
没错
Oh, yeah.
要是我男友发现你跟我说过话
My boyfriend's gonna kill you
他会杀了你的
for talking to me.
是啊  你男朋友肯定是个狠角色
Yeah, well, I'm sure that your boyfriend's a very scary person,
让他放马过来  但你得跟我走
and he's welcome to try. But you need to come with me.
不  不要
No, no.
该死  真见鬼
Damn it. Oh, shit.
我不想走  懂吗
I don't want to go, okay?
所以请告诉我妈  别再来这套了  行吗
So tell my mom to stop this shit, okay?
我是想帮你
I am trying to help you.
好吧
Okay.
混蛋  快跑吧
什么事都没有  亲爱的
别这样  别  求你了
柴德里斯就住在那个小山丘的顶上
Childress lives at the top of that hill.
这里看上去差不多已经废弃了
Most of these look abandoned.
是啊
They are.
大概十年前  这里脑子还正常的人
Chemical spill sent the sane ones running
就因为化学品泄露都跑光了
from this area about ten years ago.
怎么回事
What the hell?
谁会把一辆卡车停在路中间
Who the hell leaves a truck in the middle of the road?
还在窗户边留下一架步枪
He left one rifle in the window.
车子是注册在杰克・柴德里斯名下
Registered to Jack Childress,
住在麦克纳特路
McNutt Road.
混蛋  立刻把桑娅和马可叫来
Son of a bitch. Get Sonya and Marco down here right now.
遵命  长官
Yes, sir.
我是库珀  我们在失落的绿洲外
Hey, it's Coop. We got Childress's abandoned
找到了柴德里斯丢下的卡车
truck down here outside Lost Oasis.
请你们立刻赶来  查看情况
Come on up and let's take look.
我们在路南边400米
We're a quarter mile down the road.
杰克・柴德里斯
Hey. Jack Childress.
有消息称警方正在通缉他
Source told me the police are looking at him...
原因我还不清楚
I'm not sure what's up.
这我没料到
It's not what I expected.
什么意思
What do you mean?
他和盖德曼有什么关系
What's the connection between him and Gedman?
或者跟心理师  马可・鲁伊斯
Or the shrinker or Marco Ruiz,
23号尸体  甚至我
Body 23, me even.
我们还不能确定
We don't know yet.
跟这家伙产生交集不是巧合
There aren't...coincidences with this guy.
走吧  去他家里看看
Come on, let's go to his house.
你自己去吧
Tell you what, you go.
你难道没看出来我现在头脑不清吗
I don't know if you've noticed but my brain ain't right.
写什么报道都救不了我
I can't write a sentence to save my life, and I got...
我一直头疼得要死
I got this mother of a headache that won' go away.
对于戒酒戒毒  我的身体向我竖起了中指
My body's basically giving me the middle finger for gettin clean.
也许你该去看医生
Maybe you should go to see a doctor.
是啊  然后他会告诉我
Oh, yeah, why so he can tell me
我是个酒鬼瘾君子无药可救了
I'm an alcoholic drug addict that's all broken.
不了  谢谢
No, thanks.
弗莱  这可是关键性的报道
Frye, this is the story.
我知道
I know...
I know.
报道给你了  快去吧  战士
It's your story now. Go get them, tiger.
三秒之内捡起来没事  你吃吧
Three-second rule. You can have it.
失落的绿洲房车公园
我们两人一组  挨个房车排查
We go in pairs, trailer by trailer.
确保他没有躲在这些铁皮里
Make sure he's not hiding in any of these tin cans.
是  长官
Yes, sir.
上一次我们请求支援
Last time we called the cavalry,
一个小女孩被杀了
a little girl got killed....
谢谢
Oh, gracias.
-谢谢你  -不客气
-Thank you.  - De nada.
-汉克  -别担心
- Hank...  - Don't worry about it.
斯托克斯副警长  你来这干嘛
Deputy Stokes, what are you doing here?
我接到呼叫说有辆卡车堵在路中央
I got a call about that truck in the middle of the road.
出什么事了
What's going on?
你好  伙计
Hey, man.
有个嫌犯逃到公园里了
Uh, we got the suspect in the park here.
边桥屠夫吗
The Bridge Butcher?
曼尼  帮我一个忙
Manny, do me a favor.
封锁入口和这些卡车  好吗
Secure the entrance and the trucks, all right?
遵命
You got it.
好吧  我们走
Good deal.Let's go.
早上好
Good morning.
好戏开始了
Time to shine.
埃尔帕索警察  开门
El Paso PD,open the door.
夫人  里面有人和你在一起吗
Ma'am, is anyone else in there with you
-没有  警官  -好吧
- No, ma'am.  - All right.
西博思科特
Seabiscuit.
-夫人  -该死的
- Ma'am... - Goddamn it
请回到房间锁好门
Please go inside and lock the door.
把音乐声音调低
Turn the music down.
是浴盐
Bath salts.
伙计
Man!
没有
Nada
警官
Detectives.
我又搜了一下那卡车
I went back to the truck.
发现了这个  是一个骨锯
Found this.This is a bone saw.
用来对付野生动物  比如  鹿  害鸟
That's used for wild game, deer, vermin, whatnot.
-装进袋子  -听着
- Bag it.  - Listen.
我只是  警官
I just.. Detective!
我要把你的脸啃下来
I'll eat your face off.
那条袜子遮不住你的蛋
That sock don't ever cover your nut sack.
-不是他  -对  但他认识嫌疑人
- That's not him.  - Nope. But he knows him.
他说柴德里斯十分钟前来过这里
Says Childress through here about ten minutes ago.
他去哪了
Where was he going?
公园北角  那里有很多空地
North edge of the park. Bunch of vacants down there.
风声紧的时候他就躲在那里
He stays in 'em when he's having a crazy day.
-多久一次  -很多次
- How often is that?  - A lot!
而且那个疯子有枪
And that psycho's armed.
待着别动
Stay.
没有  没有他的踪迹
Nope, nothing. No sign of him
天这么热  他徒步不可能走太远
Well, if he's on foot he's not gonna get far in this heat.
也许有人开车接他
Or maybe he's got car waiting?
我们的跟他取得联系
We need to get contact with him.
我们要怎么做
How are we gonna do that?
给他打电话
Call him.
你真的认为他会接吗
You really think he' gonna answer?
他喜欢被人瞩目
Well, he likes the attention.
他为此时刻准备着  所以
This is what he's been preparing for, so...
-鲁伊斯警官  -什么事  副警长
- Detective Ruiz!  - Yes, Deputy?
-有什么发现吗  -没有
- You got something?  - Uh... well... no.
但是  好吧  我只是想问你个问题
But, uh, yeah. Yeah, I just... I got a quick question for you.
我不知道你是否注意到
I don't know if you noticed,
我今早把背带脱掉了
but I got my braces off this morning
我还真没注意
No, I did not notice.
其实我想说的是
Well, the reason bring it up...
当我把它们脱掉时
Well, I was in there getting 'em popped off,
背带弹开的那一刹那
and while they were popping 'em off,
我做了一个最光怪陆离的
I just had th wildest, strangest, uh..
白日梦  你肯定这么认为
daydream... I think that's what you call it.
-好吧  -是关于案子的
- Okay.. - About this case.
-行我知道了  -别走  听我说
- Yeah - No, no, no, listen.
基本上我的思路是
So... and basically what I was thinking
如果你是那个杀手
was that if you were the killer,
而且费尽周折
and you were to go to all this trouble...
-什么  -去弄这些珠子
- Yeah - ...to-to do the beads,
留下这条线索
and-and all these messages...
我操
Shit.
狗娘养的
Son of a bitch!
有人开枪  有人中枪
Shots fired! Shots fired! Man down!
躲开  躲开
Move! Move!
狗娘养的
Son of a bitch!
白皮肤  棕皮肤
White. Brown.
妈的
Shit.
快点
Come on, now.
狗娘养的
距离500码  山顶上
500 yards.Top of the hill.
他在棕色房子里
Brown house.
隐藏在水塔边
He's tucked against that water tower.
这家伙回他的房子去了
He's back in his goddamn house.
混蛋
Shit, shit.
该死  斯托克斯
Damn it, Stokes.
麦克纳特路  房车公园北侧  警员中枪
Mcnutt Road, north end of the trailer park. Officer down.
别呼叫了  咱们去抓他
Forget it!... Let's... go get him.
特警队20分钟就到
SWAT's gonna be here in 20 min.
那时候他早逃远了
He'll be gone by them.
那就赶紧去抓他
So let's go get him!
别管特警队了
Forget the SWAT!
杰克
Jack.
我是杰克请讲
You're on with jack.
我联系到他了
I got him!
好的  马可
Okay, Marco..
上吧
Come on.
小心点
Be careful!
我会分散他的注意力
I'll keep him distracted.
你仔细听我说
I need you to listen to me.
那我可说不好
Yeah, I-I don't know about that.
我看到你了
I see you.
我能杀了你
I could kill you.
这可不是体育活动
Almost isn't sporting, is it?
结束了
It's over.
是啊  结局已定
Yeah yeah, the end is already determined.
你杀了警察  警察肯定也会追捕你
You killed a cop, that means cops are coming to kill you.
你入侵我的领地了
Well, you invade my land.
或许你得后退几步
Maybe you got it backwards.
特警队正在赶来
A SWAT team's on their way.
是啊  我知道
Yep. I'm sure they are.
但是太晚了  我现在掌握主动
But they're late. I'm in control.
听着  你想讲出你的故事
Listen, you want to tell your story?
这样你可讲不了了
This is not the way to do it.
他们会杀了你的
They will kill you.
我现在还能阻止他们
I can still stop them.
头  我们要怎么办
All right, boss. How we gonna do this?
她正在和他通话
She's talking to him on the phone.
给她五分钟时间
We're gonna give her fiv minutes.
你觉得她能说服吗
You think she's gonna talk him out of anything?
就给她五分钟
Five mintues.
是  长官
Yes, sir.
你为什么不说话了  杰克
Why'd you stop talking, Jack?
你想看到我再说吗
Would it help if you could see me.
我也说不清  也好
Oh, I don't know. Yeah, sure.
-杰克  这到底是为什么  -为什么
- Tell me why, Jack. - Why?
为什么呢  因为我知道真相
Why? Because I am the truth.
真相
Truth?
埃尔帕索地区被边界  文化  历史
El Paso del Norte has been falsely split by borders,
错误的分裂
by... by cultures, by history.
无论你做什么都无法改变这一点
What you're doin won't change that.
试试才能知道
I can try.
这就是你干的事情吗
Is that what you'r doing...
完成使命
on your missions?
厉害
Impressive.
你也知道  寄生虫和宿主没有区别
Well, you know, parasite, host, same thing.
你为什么要杀这么多人  杰克
Why did you kill so many people, Jack?
一场战争正在边境上演
There is a war happening here at the border.
但人们似乎对此一无所知
And no one seems to know about it.
我想把真相公布于众
I want the truth to come out.
狗娘养的
你还有时间
You still have time.
所有的制度终将作茧自缚
All institutions eat themselves eventually.
你很聪明  应该可以明白的
You're smart, you know that.
你好啊
Hi there.
把你的枪放下
Put your gun down.
我喜欢近距离枪杀
You know, I like to kill up close.
我会开枪的
I will shoot you.
我相信你会的
I believe you will.
桑娅
Sonya!
别乱动  混蛋
老实点
Stay there!
你个狗娘养的
Son of a bitch.
放开我
Come on!
你没事吧  桑娅
You okay, Sonya?
汉克  她怎么样
Hank! Is she all right?
我没问你
I'm not asking about you!
她没事
She's all right.
她还好吗
Is she okay?
她没事
She's all right.
你还好吗
Hey. How are you?
疼的没法呼吸
Sore, can't breathe.
刚才真是
That was..
我们抓住他了  都结束了
We got him. It's over.
也许吧
Maybe.
什么意思  有什么问题
What do you mean? What's wrong?
他是疯子
He's insane.
对啊  没错  那又怎么了
Yeah, so, okay. And?
我只是不确定预谋这一切的人会是疯子
I'm just not sure that the man who planned all this is insane.
我们发现了骨锯和汽车
We have the bone saw and the car.
你也看到了书里的字迹
You saw the writing in this book.
就是他了
It's him.
警官
Officer.
你可以逃跑的
Could've run.
为什么留下了等着挨枪子
Why'd you stay to shoot?
因为任务还没完成
The job wasn't done.
什么
What?
我本想杀那个墨西哥人
I meant to kill the Mexican.
孩子们  快进屋
没关系  别管我
It's okay. Don't mind me.
出什么事了  太太
Is there something wrong, Senorita?
给你
Uh, here.
这是什么
What's this?
你的工资
That's you salary.
这个是地道的分成
And that's you cut of the tunnel.
-不用了  -我们是搭档
- It's okay. - We're partners.
我猜卡尔之前没给过你吧
I assume you didn't have this raise with Karl.
没有
No.
谢谢
还有什么心事吗  太太
Is there something else, Senorita?
你觉得我做得对吗
Do you think I'm doing the right thing?
我觉得你别无选择
I think you're doing the only thing.
你朋友在这会待多久
How long is your friend staying?
雷
Ray?
不知道
I don't know.
他帮我处理和格雷西拉的生意
He's helping me deal with Graciela.
我听说了
I heard.
你信任他吗
Do you trust him?
信任  怎么了
I think I do. Why?
没什么
It's nothing.
我们是搭档  说实话
We're partners. Say it.
我觉得让他和格雷西拉打交道
I don't think it's such a good idea
不是什么好事
to let him deal with Graciela.
她和卡尔原来有一套管理办法
Senorita, her and Karl had a way of controlling.
谢谢你给的钱
我会告诉雷小心点
I'll tell Ray to be careful.
晚安  凯撒
Good night, Caesar.
晚安
穿梭在
Traveling through...
《野火》
"Prairie Fire"?
斯托克斯是个蠢货
Stokes was a moron,
但不应该被爆头这么惨
but he didn't deserve to get his head blowed off.
给自己几天时间
Take a couple of days.
好吧
Yes, sir.
我们抓住他了  这就行了
We found him. That's what matters.
是吗
Is it?
那家伙完全疯了
That dude is gone complete insanity
他会在狱中被殴打  织袜子度过余生
and spends the rest of his life beating off and knitting socks.
要真是那样  也就那样了
Well, that's what happens, that's what happens.
桑娅真该朝他的额头开枪
Sonya should've shot him between the eyes.
那他就被打死了
Yeah, and that would've made him dead.
我不觉得那样有什么问题  汉克
I don't see the problem with that, Hank.
过上十五年再看看
Give it 15 years.
天呐
Oh, God.
-我能信任你吗  -当然了  宝贝
- Can I trust you? - Of course, baby.
我能信任你吗
Can I trust you?
放心吧
Yeah
射在里面
Come inside me.
你确定
You sure?
不  没有好点
No, not better.
我  我其实觉得更糟了
I would, uh... I would definitely classify it a worse, actually.
我当然会帮你跟进报道的
Well, yeah, of course I'll help you file your story.
不  我不去酒吧  我要去
No, I'm not going to the bar. I'm gonna...